# Aditya Mukherjee

# Full-Stack Software Developer

I am a keen learner, flexible, reliable and possess good time keeping skills. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as independently. My quest for learning and enhancing my knowledge never dwindles. Being a sportsperson I am very well experienced in handling challenging and pressure



adityamukherjee2106@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/aditya-mukherjee-984380187

. 8808215901

github.com/Adi2106

## **EDUCATION**

## B.Tech(CSE)

Abdul Kalam Technical University - Krishna **Engineering College** 

07/2018 - Present

9.4 CGPA ≅ 94% (Till 6th Semester)

## ISC(12TH)

Boys' High School & College, Prayagraj

08/2017 - 08/2018 Percentage-88%

# **PROJECTS**

My Portfolio Website

https://adi2106.github.io/MyPortfolio

Enfec Admin Portal (09/2021 - Present)

https://enfec-admin-portal.netlify.app/

Netflix Clone containing metadata (05/2021 - 06/2021)

https://adityasnetflixclone.netlify.app.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer

Samsung R&D Institue

01/2022 - Present

Noida

- Description
- FOTA and Google Messaging Services
- Backend Android development
- Rest Apis and Microservices

# JAVA SOFTWARE DEVELOPER(FULL STACK)

**Enfec Solutions** 06/2021 - 12/2021

Hyderabad

Description And Accomplishments

- Top Performer averaging 96% in weekly assessments.
- Hands on experience in J2SE and J2EE
- Java Servlets using Apache Tomcat 8.5 server.
- Spring framework version 5.3 using STS IDE
- Building end to end applications using standard principals of RestApi's and Microservices.
- Using Postman for debugging and implementing
- Integration testing using Junit and Mockito framework.
- Using Java Selenium for automation.

# **SKILLS**

ReactJS Java JavaScript Bootstrap Node Js DSA Express Js Selenium Android

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### National Level Shuttler (2017)

Have been a winner of State Level Badminton Tournament and have represented my state at National level.

#### University Topper (2018 - 2019)

Secured first position in my university in the Academic year 2018-19

#### Mr. Versatile (02/2018)

Was bestowed the title of Mr. Versatile in the farewell ceremony of my School

#### Mr. Fresher (09/2018)

Was bestowed with the title of Mr. Fresher in the freshers function of my college.

#### Best Debater (2018 - 2020)

Was the winner in debate competition in college for two years consecutively.

# RESPONSIBILITIES

#### Student Placement Coordinator (01/2020 - 06/2022)

My responsibility is to manage and communicate with various companies approaching our college.

#### College Cultural Vice Captain (2017 - 2018)

Lead my School in various Cultural and Sports extravaganza.

#### Deputy Secretary General (01/2019 - 06/2022)

Was given the position of Deputy Secretary General in Model United Nations society in my college.

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Design and Analysis of Algorithms (8 weeks under IIT Kanpur)

JAVA(Udemy)

Google Cloud Fundamentals(Google)

Backend Web Development with NodeJs (Google Developers Club Ranchi)